uipath.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

This policy together with our [Terms of Use](https://www.uipath.com/legal/terms-of-use) of this website and any other documents we mention in this policy is meant to inform you on which personal data about you we collect, use, disclose, share or otherwise process when you are using this website, our products and our services. Please read this policy carefully to understand our views and practices on how we protect your personal data.

## 1\. ABOUT US

UiPath and our existing or future affiliates (collectively “UiPath” or “we”) are the controllers with respect to your data. This means that we determine the purpose and manner in which your personal data is processed, as specified in this Policy.

UiPath is the entity deciding for what purpose and through what means your data is processed. See here more about who and where we are.

UiPath SRL, which is a legal entity organized and existing under the laws of Romania with registered office at 4 Vasile Alecsandri Street, 11 Daniel Constantin Street, 5th floor, building A, district 1, Bucharest, Romania is the contact entity for any questions regarding how your personal data is being processed.

If you want to know more information regarding UiPath entities and locations please visit https://www.uipath.com/contact-us.

## 2\. WHAT DO WE UNDERSTAND BY PERSONAL DATA?

Personal data is the information related to a natural person and which can be used to identify that person such as name, email address, telephone number, social media usernames, location data or business titles.

Personal data is data about you which you provide to us when interacting with UiPath through our website and by using our products and services and which helps us know who you are.

This means that when you use our products, services and website, we will collect certain information about you (“personal data”) which can identify you directly (name, email) or indirectly (IP address or other online identifier). We also collect anonymous information and aggregated data regarding user behavior, navigational information, device information, which helps us tailor our services and understand usage trends.

## 3\. WHAT PERSONAL DATA IS PROCESSED AND WHY?

The personal data we process, as well as the purposes and legal basis for such processing, will differ depending on your relationship with UiPath:

#### When you create a UiPath account

Your UiPath account is a single sign on which helps you log into several UiPath platforms using the same credentials. If you decide to log in with Facebook or other social media account, remember that UiPath will have access to your Facebook profile data.

UiPath uses Microsoft cloud services as an identity provider for authentication services and identity management. This will help you access other UiPath websites easier, by using the same credentials and provides you with more security when accessing your account. In order to connect to UiPath, your email and name are required. This means that changing your e-mail address means creating a new UiPath account. Please remember that when you use social media accounts to connect to UiPath, you agree to have your social media profile data, such as your name, telephone number, friends, photo, birthday, gender, location, interests, shared with UiPath, through an Application Programming Interface (API).

#### If You are an Academy User

  * In order for you to become an Academy User and to manage your account, including sending you information regarding your courses, subscription, certifications or payments we process your username, email, first and last name, language, phone number, payment information, country, employer for performing the [contract](https://www.uipath.com/rpa/academy/terms-of-use) you signed with us;
  * In order to share your performance in Academy with your employer or with a company of your choosing , we process your username, email, first and last name, country, employer/company, user performance for the execution of the [contract](https://www.uipath.com/academy-terms-of-use)  with your employer and with your express consent ;
  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest we process your email based on your express consent;
  * In order to confirm to a third party that a certification is provided by UiPath, we process your name and e-mail, in our legitimate interest to make sure that our certifications are fairly used;

When you create an account in Academy we process certain personal data about you as a result of agreeing with the Terms & Conditions. These data are used to manage your account, to share or confirm your progress and to keep you updated.

  * In order to better understand navigational trends on our website, we process the browser information, device used, IP address and user experience on our website (see section 4 of this policy for the analytical tools we use) based on your express consent and in order to improve your experience on our website and when you are using our services.
  * In order to provide you on site trainings, your name, e-mail address and company will be processed as part of implementing the UiPath Training Partner Agreement.

Academy is built on Docebo platform, which is a processor on behalf of UiPath. For more information check Docebo’s Privacy Policy [ here.](https://www.docebo.com/docebo-privacy-policy/)

#### If You obtain a certification through our Certification Platform

  * In order for you to use the online certification platform, test your RPA knowledge and obtain the certificate we process certain personal data about you;
  * In order to create and manage your account and certification, we collect certain categories of personal identifiable information about you such as: full name, employment type/status, country, job title, RPA experience and test performance, job title, email address, employer, payment details, username. This information is processed in order to perform the contract you have with us, to register, evaluate your performance, provide the certification and manage your account;

In order for you to become a certified professional to deliver an RPA solution, UiPath processes certain categories of personal data about you.

  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest we process your email based on your express consent;
  * UiPath only uses essential cookies, meaning the ones required for the functioning and security of your account, on the online certification platform.

  * In order to send you information related to your certification or to confirm or send, upon your request, the information related to your certification to third-parties, we process personal data about you;
  * In order to confirm to a third party that a certification is provided by UiPath, we process your name and e-mail, in our legitimate interest to make sure that our certifications are fairly used.

#### If You are a UiPath Community Edition User

When you download UiPath Community Edition, personal data is required in order to perform the terms and conditions of use and for managing your account.

  * In order for you to become a UiPath Community Edition User and for managing your account and providing you with relevant information, we process your username, email, first and last name, field of expertise, job title, employer, industry, country, Twitter username and LinkedIn Profile URL (if you choose to provide them) for performing your[ contract](https://www.uipath.com/developers/community-edition/license-agreement) with us regarding your free trial of the software;

  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent;
  * In order to improve product functionality and in order to provide you access to information regarding process execution errors, we may receive confidential or personal data as part of the images received by us when you enable these features, based on your agreement with the terms of use;

#### If You are an RPA Enterprise Platform Trial User

  * In order for you to become a Trial User and for you to receive information regarding your license subscription, release notes and for providing technical support related to your account, we process your username, email, first and last name, field of expertise, job title, employer, industry, Twitter username and LinkedIn Profile URL and phone number for performing your [contract](https://www.uipath.com/hubfs/legalspot/21-06-17-Trial-General-Terms.pdf?t=1536650668872) with us;
  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent;

When you download UiPath RPA Enterprise Platform, personal data is required in order to perform the terms and conditions of use.

  * In order to improve product functionality and in order to provide you access to information regarding process execution errors, we may receive confidential or personal data as part of the images received by us when you enable these features, based on your agreement with the terms of use;

#### If You are a Community Forum User

  * In order for you to become a Community Forum User, we process your username, email, first and last name, employer, industry, Twitter username and LinkedIn Profile URL, country, photo and phone number for performing your [contract](https://forum.uipath.com/tos) with us;
  * In order to manage your Community Forum account, including sending information regarding your license subscription, release notes and providing you with your technical support for your Community account, we process your username, email, first and last name, browser information, for performing your [contract](https://forum.uipath.com/tos) with us;
  * In order to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent;

When you use UiPath Forum personal data about you will be processed for managing your account and for you to receive updates and news. Please remember that the Forum is public, when providing your real name, photo and location.

  * In order to better understand navigational trends on our website, we process the browser information, device used, IP address and user experience on the website (see section 4 of this policy for the analytical tools we use) based on your consent and in order to improve your experience on our website and when you are using our services.
  * If you decide to log in with Google, please have in mind that your Google profile information will be shared with UiPath.

If you decide to log in with Google, please have in mind that your Google profile information will be shared with UiPath.

UiPath Forum is developed on the Discourse platform, which is a processor on behalf of UiPath. Please find [ here ](https://www.discourse.org/privacy)the Privacy Policy of Discourse.

#### If You are an Enterprise User and You contact us for technical support and activations

If you request technical support from UiPath we will require some identification data from you. Please try not to send us any personal or confidential information, except from your identification data and relevant technical data when asking for technical support.

  * In order to manage your technical support request related to UiPath Studio, UiPath Robot or UiPath Orchestrator, we process your name, email, country and device ID for performing the contract (the End User Licensing Agreement) you signed with us;
  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent;
  * In order to respond to your requests when engaging with us through our call center, we record your voice and process your name, email, company name and region, based on your consent.

  * In order to better understand the navigational trends on our website, we process the Browser information, device used, IP address and user experience on the website (see section 4 of this policy for the analytical tools we use), based on your consent in order to improve your experience on our website and your user experience when you are using our services.

Zendesk is a processor on behalf of UiPath and provides our ticketing platform. Please read more about Zendesk’s Privacy Policy [here.](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/)

#### If You are attending our hackathons, webinars and events

  * In order to register to our events, webinars and hackathons, we process your personal data such as your name, surname, email address, telephone number, location, social media account, job title, company, voice, image, based on your acceptance to participate and based on agreeing with our event terms and conditions;
  * In order to provide you with follow-up information after an event you have attended or to ask for your feedback, we process your email, based on your agreement to participate at our events;

When you attend UiPath events, we require your personal data for registration. In our terms and conditions for participating at our events we make it clear that we like to make videos and take photos. Please let us know if you do not want to appear in our photos or videos.

  * In order for you to receive further news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent;
  * In order to transfer your contact information to our Partners or Sponsors to our events and webinars, we process your name, your email and company email, based on your consent;
  * In order to provide you with relevant information about RPA and other things of interest to you we share your personal information such as name, email address, company or employment status with our partners, based on your consent.

For organizing these events we use the services of different contractors which are data processors on our behalf or which are data controllers themselves. Please check their privacy policies when registering for our events.

When UiPath is a sponsor or partner at events organized by third parties, UiPath may receive your personal data, such as name, email, company name, if you agreed to receiving communications and having your data shared with UiPath.

#### If You take part in our contests and campaigns

In order for you to participate in UiPath’s campaigns and contests and in order for us to provide you the prize, we process personal data, including sensitive data such as your ID information, for compliance with applicable laws and policies.

  * In order to participate in our campaigns and win our prizes we process personal data about you such as your name, surname, email address, telephone number, national identification number, based on our legal financial obligations and on our legitimate interest to comply with our internal financial policies;
  * In order to promote you as the winner of our campaign we may process your name, surname, testimonials and photo, based on your consent;

  * In order for you to receive further news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent.

#### If you are a UiPath Go! and Connect user

If you use UiPath Go! you will also have a UiPath Connect profile, which means you can have access to and you can create activities and assets using RPA as well as share your RPA achievements with other RPA users. Both profiles are public, except for your e-mail. In order to create and manage your profile/account we will require certain personal data about you, as part of complying with the terms and conditions and for you to enjoy all features of the platforms.

  * • In order for you to create an account on UiPath GO! and UiPath Connect, for managing your account and in order to promote, upload, download RPA applications, activities, workflows or other assets, as well as for sharing your expertise and engaging with other RPA enthusiasts, we process personal data about you such as: full name, employment type/status, country, job title, RPA experience, social media profile, email address, employer, photo, location, based on your acceptance of the terms and conditions of use;
  * In order for you to receive news about other UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest we process your email based on your express consent;

  * For analytics purposes and for a better understanding of navigational trends on our website, we process the browser information, device used, IP address and user experience on our website (see section 4 of this policy for the analytical tools we use) based on your consent and in order to improve your experience on our website and when you are using our services;
  * In order to ask you for feedback and to send you communications related to the assets you are using as well as in connection with your account and activities on our platforms, we process your email address and name based on your use of the service and on your notification preferences;
  * In order to verify that the personal data provided for your company account is correct, we process your personal data, such as your email, job title, company, based on the performance of your agreement (terms and conditions of the service) with UiPath;
  * In order for you to be able to use all features of the service we collect data regarding your social engagement on our platforms, such as posts, comments, videos, photos, as part of providing our services and in our legitimate interest to improve your experience when using these services;
  * In order for you to enjoy Connect’s career paths, your progress level in Academy and Forum will be displayed in your Connect profile;
  * In order to honor your requests to contact different authors we share your personal data with the authors of your choosing, based on your express consent.

Please note that you have the same profile on UiPath Go! and on UiPath Connect and that this profile is public, including your badges and achievements, except for your email address.

Platform OS is the platform which we use for the development of UiPath Go! and UiPath Connect and which is a processor on behalf of UiPath. Check [ here](https://www.platform-os.com/privacy) its Privacy Policy.

#### If You are a UiPath Partner

If you have a business partnership with UiPath or in order to become a business partner of UiPath we require and process certain personal data from you as the partner’s representatives, which enables you to use our partner portal.

  * In order to process your request for becoming a UiPath Partner, we process your full name, company, job title, location, email in our legitimate interest to assess our business partners and in order to provide you with an answer to your inquiry;
  * In order to create and manage your account on the partner portal, we process your full name, job title, company, email, as a result of performing your contract with UiPath;

  * In order for you to receive news about other UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest we process your email based on your express consent;
  * For analytics purposes and for a better understanding of navigational trends on our website, we process the browser information, device used, IP address and user experience on our website (see section 4 of this policy for the analytical tools we use) based on your consent and in order to improve your experience on our website and when you are using our services.

Zinfi is the platform which we use for the development of the Partner Portal and which is a processor on behalf of UiPath. Check [ here ](https://www.zinfi.com/privacy-policy/)its Privacy Policy.

#### If You are a Website Visitor

If you visit our website, we collect personal data about you with your consent in order to send you relevant news and to improve your experience on our website.

  * In order to better understand navigational trends on our website, we process the browser information, device used, IP address and user experience on the website (see section 4 of this policy for the analytical tools we use) based on your consent and in order to improve your experience on our website and when you are using our services;

  * If You contact us / subscribe to our newsletters, events, blog and other news and communications we process your email address, based on your consent and in order to send you the latest news and blog posts;
  * In order for us to manage the inquiries you submit to UiPath using our Contact Forms, we process your name, email, phone number, job level, field of expertise, employer, industry, country, Twitter username and LinkedIn Profile URL based on our legitimate interest to respond to your inquiry, provide you with more information and answer your questions satisfactory;
  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent.

#### If You want to join our Academic Alliance Program

Please have in mind that for all UiPath products and services which you are using you are responsible for keeping the data accurate. If you are posting or uploading personal data of someone, please make sure that you have all consents for doing this.

  * In order for you to contact us and to join our program we gather personal data about you such as full name, e-mail, telephone number, institution, position or occupation, location, based on your consent or based on performing the contract we have in place with your employer;

  * In order for you to receive news about UiPath products, services, events and promotions tailored to your interest, we process your email based on your express consent;
  * We may also receive data about you from our business partners with your consent. You will be informed when your data reaches us.

Our website is developed on the Hubspot platform. Please check its [ Privacy Policy.](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy?__hstc=71912524.f8af3daf926d37ac536565d001cbf373.1536650751982.1536650751982.1536650751982.1&__hssc=71912524.1.1536650751983&__hsfp=872972226)

## 4\. WHAT ANALYTICS TOOLS DO WE USE?

In order to understand the navigational trends on our website we use third-party analytics tools which collect information which your browser sends when you visit our web page. Here are tools which we use and information about their privacy policies:

  * **Hubspot** uses the information collected according to its [Privacy Policy](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy?__hstc=71912524.f8af3daf926d37ac536565d001cbf373.1536650751982.1536650751982.1536650751982.1&__hssc=71912524.1.1536650751983&__hsfp=872972226), which also contains indications on how to unsubscribe.
  * **Twitter Advertising** uses the information collected according to its [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy), which also includes information on how to unsubscribe.
  * **DoubleClick Ad Exchange** is a Google product. Its policy and contact information can be found [here](https://support.google.com/adxbuyer/answer/1325008?hl=en).
  * **Google Tag Manager** is a Google analytics solution. The way Google uses the information collected can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy).
  * **Google Analytics tool** is also reflected in the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy), where you can also find information about your ads settings.
  * **LinkedIn Analytics** use of the information collected can be found in its [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy).
  * **Hotjar** uses information collected according to its [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy), where you can also find opt-out information.

When you visit our website and if you accept our cookies we collect certain data about navigational trends and about you, which helps us improve our services and our online presence.

  * **Cookies**   
When you are visiting our website, we are using cookies, a small software file stored temporarily or placed on the hard drive of your device in order to allow a web server to identify your device and the web browser you use, in order to recognize you when you are visiting the site again. Cookies may also store preferences or other information about you. For more information please visit our [ Cookie Policy.](https://www.uipath.com/legal/cookies-policy)

## 5\. DO WE USE AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING AND PROFILING?

For direct marketing purposes and in order to send you news about UiPath products and activities that are tailored to your interests, we gather data about you through cookies or similar technologies with your consent. For our business purposes we build individual profiles in order to send you relevant offerings. You may be denied access to our services in order to comply with our export control regulations.

As a result of our obligations regarding export control regulations, we will deny access to our services or products if you or your company are among the ones listed on the relevant websites.

In order to send you information about our products, events, news and activities, tailored to your interests we build individual profiles from the personal data you provided to us (such as name, company, job title, social media), from navigational information, information regarding the use of our services and information provided by our partners about you.

We do this in order to maximize your experience with our products and to make available to you personalized offers of your liking. We always rely on your consent for our direct marketing activities.

We also use personal data, such as online behavior data, for statistical purposes, in order to help us improve the way we promote our products.

You can oppose to this anytime by writing at  [privacy@uipath.com](mailto:privacy@uipath.com)

We do not use profiling or automated decision making on children’s personal data.

## 6\. TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?

For the purposes described in this policy we use the services of various contractors, mainly digital service providers. Some of them were mentioned in the section above. These contractors process specific categories of personal data on our behalf to help us organize events, manage clients’ information and contracts, store data, analyze and organize data.

In order for you to benefit from quality services and products we engage contractors to process data on our behalf. These contractors are bound by confidentiality and other contractual requirements to keep your data safe and secure. When the law requires, data is also shared with public authorities.

With each of these contractors we have contractual agreements which ensure that your personal data is protected and that the processing of personal data is limited to the minimum necessary to perform the contracted services. We make sure that our contractors do not process your data for other purposes than those for which we agreed. We make every effort to ensure that all the entities we are working with are storing your personal data in safe locations and that they implement proper security measures. Some of our contractors are also controllers on their own, such as Google LLC carrying out processing activities while using their services and products, which include online advertising technologies, search engine, cloud computing. Check out Google’s  [ Privacy Policy ](https://policies.google.com/privacy)for more information.

Some of the contractors are third parties who are not intended to process the personal data but may have access to it upon fulfilling their tasks or interacting with us, such as technical maintenance companies, financial or legal auditors.

#### We may also provide personal data to third parties in the following situations:

  * to public authorities, auditors or institutions competent to exercise inspections on UiPath, which may ask us to provide information, based on their legal obligations. Such public authorities or institutions may be relevant data protection authorities or authorities for consumer protection;
  * to comply with a legal requirement or to protect the rights and assets of UiPath or other entities or people, such as courts of law;
  * to third parties’ acquirers, if UiPath’s business would be subject to a change of control or other similar procedure or acquisition and your personal data would be part of the transaction.

India, Japan, Germany, France, United Kingdom, Netherlands, United Arab Emirates, Singapore, South Korea, Spain, Sweden, China, companies which respect the same standards of personal data protection. For more information regarding the UiPath group, please visit  www.uipath.com.

## 7\. DO WE TRANSFER YOUR PERSONAL DATA ABROAD?

UiPath is a global company so your data is shared with UiPath’s affiliates or with UiPath’s processors around the world. We make sure that your data is kept and transferred safely, by respecting European legal requirements for data transfers.

In the context of completing the purposes presented to you in this policy, your personal data may be transferred abroad to states in the European Union **(“EU”)** , European Economic Area **(the “EEA”)** or to third countries.

Any transfer performed by UiPath will respect the legal requirements laid down by the European data protection legislation.

In what concerns data transfers to third countries, we make sure that appropriate safeguards are in place in order to keep your data secure.

## 8\. FOR HOW LONG DO WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?

UiPath will store your data only for the period of time necessary or required by law. If you have entered into a contract with UiPath we will store your data for up to 5 years or as long as it is required by law, after the termination of the agreement with us.

We will store your personal data only for the period of time necessary in order to achieve the purposes described to you in this policy and in accordance with our legal obligations, our contractual obligations or the industry practices.

We will make sure not to keep excessive or irrelevant data, such as data which is out of date. We will also constantly review the periods of time for which the different categories of data we process are retained.

After the duration of the processing expires and UiPath no longer has legal or legitimate reasons to process your personal data, the data will be deleted in accordance with its procedures, which may involve archiving, anonymizing or destroying it. For using UiPath products and services we store your data up to 5 years from the termination of our agreement with you, except for the cases when legal requirements state otherwise.

## 9\. DO WE PROCESS PERSONAL DATA FROM CHILDREN?

We sometimes process personal data from children in order to spread the RPA knowledge and develop educational partnerships.

Under certain circumstances we process personal data from children, attending our workshops or educational programs, respecting all applicable legislation.

## 10\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR DATA SECURE?

UiPath cares about the security of your personal data. Therefore, UiPath implements an information security framework accordance to its security certifications.

UiPath constantly evaluates and upgrades the security measures implemented as to ensure a secure and safe personal data processing. UiPath is ISO 27001 certified, regarding the security of information management. Among the measures implemented by UiPath for data protection are: physical security measures, access control management, data management control, organisational security measures and incident management procedures.

#### What happens if you don’t agree to your personal data being processed?

If you refuse to have your data processed, depending on your relationship with us, we might not be able to provide you with our products or services, send you newsletters, information about our events or other offerings, we won’t be able to enter into a contract with you, or otherwise interact with you as described in this policy.

## 11\. WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?

#### When we process your personal data, it is very important to know that you have the following rights:

  * **The right of access** to the personal data we process about you: you have the right to obtain a confirmation whether or not we process your personal data, and, if so, to have access to the type of personal data and to the conditions of processing, by sending us a request in this regard;
  * **The right to request the rectification or erasure of personal data** : you have the right to request, the rectification of inaccurate or incomplete personal data which we have about you, or the erasure of your personal data in case (i) the data are no longer necessary for their original purpose (and no new lawful purpose exists), (ii) we initially process your data based on your consent and you withdraw your consent and therefore no awful ground exists anymore, (iii) you object and we have no overriding grounds for continuing the processing, (iv) the data have been processed unlawfully, (v) erasure is necessary for compliance with EU law or Romanian law, or (vi) the data were collected from children

You can always contact UiPath at [privacy@uipath.com](mailto:privacy@uipath.com) to ask for your rights regarding the processing of your personal data by UiPath, such as the right to access your personal data, to receive a copy, to oppose to marketing communications, to have your data rectified or deleted. You can always use this form: <https://www.uipath.com/legal/personal-data> .

  * **The right to request the restriction of processing** : you have the right to ask for the restriction of processing in cases where: (i) you consider that the personal data processed is inaccurate, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of the personal data; (ii) the processing is unlawful, however you don’t want us to erase your personal data, but to restrict the use of data; (iii) in case we no longer need your personal data for the purposes we described in this policy, but you are requiring the data for establishing, exercising or defending a legal claim or (iv) you have objected to processing pending the verification whether our legitimate grounds prevail;

  * **The right to withdraw your consent for processing** , when the processing is based on your consent, without affecting the lawfulness of processing undertaken until that moment;
  * **The right to object to the data processing** on grounds related to your particular situation, when the processing is based on legitimate interest and to object at any moment to the data processing for direct marketing purposes, including profiling;
  * **The right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling** , which produces legal effects for your similarly affect you in a significant manner;
  * **The right to data portability** , meaning the right to receive your personal data, which you provided us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and the right to transfer those data to another controller, if the processing is based on your consent or the performance of a contract and is undertaken by using automatic means;
  * **The right to file a complaint** with the Data Protection Authority [(ANSPDCP)](http://dataprotection.ro/?page=contact&lang=ro) and **the right to address to the competent courts of law**.

You may exercise your rights at any time.

For any questions regarding your rights please write to us at [privacy@uipath.com](mailto:privacy@uipath.com). Also, in case you wish to withdraw your consent given for direct marketing purposes you have the possibility to use the “unsubscribe” option provided to you in every marketing communication.

## 12\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may be changed and updated by us from time to time as it could become necessary.

We will post the updates here so we encourage you to check this page.

We will notify you of any substantial changes to this Privacy Policy and will ensure that the notification is made in a way which ensures that you acknowledge them, for example by use of the email address that you have provided to us, or any other appropriate means that ensure effective communication.

If you do not agree with the changes, please contact us or deactivate your account.

## 13\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US FOR PRIVACY PURPOSES?

You may address any question regarding this document to who may be contacted using the following contact details: [privacy@uipath.com](mailto:privacy@uipath.com)or complete the online form available [ here.](https://www.uipath.com/legal/personal-data)
